travelfusion.com 2013-11-27

# Privacy Policy | Travel Search System Privacy Policy | Travelfusion

## Travelfusion Privacy Policy

Travelfusion takes the privacy of its customers very seriously. Please read this Privacy Statement, which sets out our Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy sets out the terms which govern the collection, retention and processing of your personal information which we receive when you use www.Travelfusion.com, localised Travelfusion web sites and the Travelfusion white labels (collectively, 'Site'). If our Privacy Policy changes, we will let you know the date of the latest update at the bottom of this page.

By disclosing your personal information to us using this Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Statement.

If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices or if at any time you believe that we have not adhered to the principles outlined below, please notify us by email to help@Travelfusion.com or use the feedback form so that we can deal promptly with any problem.

## Information collected

Travelfusion primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a highly personalised and interactive service that meets your needs and make your experience more relevant.

To fully participate in our services, you will need to register using our online registration form, where you will be required to provide us with your name, email, User ID and other optional personal information.

We also collect information automatically about your visit to the Site and any information you publish or services you request.

We automatically track certain information based upon your behaviour on our Site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand and serve you and our community.

We may sometimes ask you for additional information by way of surveys so that we can better understand the needs of our users to help us improve our features. Travelfusion sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party without user's express consent.

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information Travelfusion collects from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, different rules may apply. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

## Use of personal information

We analyse the behaviour of our users, identifying their demographic characteristics and personal interests. To do this, we use the personal data, which you provide to us when you use the site. This analysis allows us to optimise the service we can offer to you by knowing in advance your personal interests and preferences. This also allows us to match between users with common interests. User on the Site are only identified by their User ID and any messages are facilitated by us hiding the email addresses.

Personal information also allows us to generate interesting and personalised advertising in relation to goods and services in which you might be interested.

## Use of cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on http://www.cookiecentral.com/

We may use 'cookies' to identify you when you visit this web site and to allow registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the site and have access to information about their account.

We may also use cookies to keep track of your browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile.

## Disclosures

We will only disclose your personal information to other companies in the Travelfusion Limited group of companies, purchasers of our business and suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf. We may also disclose information to a Licensed Credit Reference Agency.

## Internet-based transfers

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing this web site and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.
